[Music]
Cole you okay I'm fine
Gio when's dinner Gio I set the table
fancy
I'm not even sure what we've got to eat
around here bonsel huh whatever I don't
eat much anyway and I don't cook much
cole was the real Chef in this place but
his old teacher mysterious voice calling
out to him to follow had to be important
right unless it was a trap and Cole's
never coming back why do you say stuff
like
that anyhow if dinner isn't ready maybe
you have time to check out the new
arrivals another crash Geer brought some
more lost items yep bunch of new stuff
just turned up new stuff means more
stuff to make
art and that's way more fun than making
[Music]
dinner I just love the smell of new old
stuff in the
morning wo check this
out kind of looks familiar you have
another piece of that thing in our art
yard right they must go together
companion
piece there it's like a set cool yep
like a family Al together like us well
us when Cole gets back if he gets back
really
a cloud can't be lost can it to you
that's no Cloud it's a city might be the
cloud Kingdom Cole told me about he said
the cloud monks there were nice
they don't look very nice l in me and
know so much to see together
we
[Music]
we be for what's
F Aaron look
out wait we mean no harm
you listen to me I speak
[Music]
dragon he did not like whatever you said
Wildfire what's his problem maybe he
thinks we broke into his house I'd be a
little peeve too
[Music]
thanks come on if my vision was right
the teacher we need is supposed to be on
the other side of that
gate feels like it's sealed shut we need
to find whatever's keeping it from
opening that bucket
this Landscaping choice is not battle
friendly these aren't ordinary Boulders
they look like they were put here on
purpose it does look like they were put
here on
purpose what are you doing Lloyd I'm
pretty sure if that basket is way down
by the boulders it'll pull the chain and
open the gate it was set up this way on
purpose but that's not going to happen
if the dragon keeps blocking the stones
let's work together some of us distract
the dragon the rest of us get those
rocks
Sora you're
up scar world record got it Sora I've
always got you Aaron
[Music]
it's
working cover
[Music]
me one more poker should be enough to
open it for us to get through on it
Lloyd
ooh am I going over here or over
here oh I was going a secret Third Way
oh come
[Music]
on I got this
Aaron great work come on
[Music]
okay okay two dragons might be a lot but
we can take him doesn't look like we
have much of a choice Kai get
ready what are they
doing this is awkward is there some kind
of social queue I'm not picking up on
you're the dragon expert are dragons
known for attacking people then suddenly
being cool with them sure if the people
they attacked fell off a cliff to their
Doom so we're not fighting anymore
congratulations sport you passed all
three tests up
high three tests the test of fears the
test of faith and the test of
unity most people don't get past the
first one
fears you mean that cave that monster
thing with the tentacles on our heads
the leap of faith through the fog into
the unknown then my favorite test Unity
like teamwork to get those stones in the
basket you ninja are tight I'm glad we
passed the test but we're looking for an
ancient Master do you know where this
teacher
is you aren't the sharpest shuriken in
the Armory are
[Music]
you what he means is we are the teachers
you're looking for I'm ronu and that's
eal we are the Dragon
Masters should we ask them what they
want sure what do you want
[Music]
they came all the way here to beat up
Gio
unexpected get the cover they aren't
friendly yeah figure that I don't know
what you want but you're going to have
to go through me to get
it you aren't alone Gio we all protect
each
other if you're not going to get to
cover then here use these
[Music]
hey
ugly oh no you seem to be
stuck hey I need my
head I'm thinking being attacked by wolf
costume people for no reason reason is
weird but maybe I'm just
naive no you're right super weird I'll
try to fuse up some
weapons this is a
weapon okay not my best
work H does the
trick this is getting ridiculous how
many these punks are
there I'm guessing enough to take over
the cloud
Kingdom spit FR they took Bono well
you're not taking us we'll face
clowns huh guess they listen to you they
don't want us they want Bonzo don't they
know we can't leave the land of lost
things doesn't seem like they're worried
about that
let her
go what
now leave her
alone Cole you're
back the legendary teacher is two
dragons dragons can be
ninja dragons make the best ninja I
swore off training non- dragons
centuries ago too many terrible
experiences why did you come here no one
has even attempted the tests in ages
this might sound wild but I got a vision
that we had to come a vision from The
Source dragons huh you came all this way
to lie Source dragons do not get
involved with Mortal matters it would
require a very dire situation for them
to do so
maybe this is that situation we need to
learn how to fight against shatter spin
why there's no one alive who can perform
that technique boy I wish that was true
you've seen someone using shatter spin
we got our butts kicked by it we had no
way to fight back more rubbish the
secrets of shatter spin have been erased
from history there is no way anyone
could learn it not anymore we're telling
you our enemy RW train trained an
elemental Master to do it Ross has these
weird wolf masks in a special gong he's
going to use them to freeze some group
called The Forbidden
five if what you're saying is true then
this world is about to face evil the
likes of which you cannot imagine
[Music]
got it good timing
call you okay
[Music]
that should buy us some time looks like
I picked an exciting day to come back
was your mission successful I'll fill
you in later we got to get to cover
[Music]
well for what it's worth it's good to
see you again Cole yeah we really missed
your breakfast you told me you like my
breakfast well compared to eating
nothing I thought it'd be boring back
here without me sorry this probably
isn't the homecoming you were hoping for
I'm just glad I arrived in time now I've
got to figure out what's up with the
cloud Kingdom
apparently these forbidden five were
only ever beaten once before and then
exiled what's so funny was there a joke
I hate missing jokes no joke we're well
aware of the fate of the Forbidden five
we are the ones who defeated
them you're the force from the East we
were told about I assumed that was just
a legend or something our Acts were
legendary Millennia
ago I'm sure that's surprising to
someone who didn't even know dragons
could be
ninja we defeated the Forbidden five and
their shatter spin with a fighting style
we created The Rising Dragon
technique then we used an extremely
powerful spell to Exile the five forever
after that we hid their language and any
mention of them I guess Lord Rob has
unhit it this Ros might have
rediscovered their teachings but the
Forbidden five can never return not even
during the ritual of the blood
moon those wolf Warriors aren't here for
random
kidnapping they have to want bonsel for
some specific reason
bonsel can you think of any reason why
they might be doing this I really don't
know I've never seen them in my life
life they're going to break through I
got this
[Music]
good luck breaking through that they
don't have a chance not with your powers
Gio getting the component should not
have been this much trouble especially
once I removed the boundary spell but of
course an elemental Master had to
interfere calm yourself Jordana but Lord
Ro she's the key I am well aware of that
prepare the gong of
[Music]
shattering what about the consequences
of using it too much isn't this risky no
cost is too high to get what we came
for do it
[Music]
[Applause]
huh something weird is happening with
the wolf
guys what is
that what do you think they're talking
about I guess the end of the world M let
me B fire not joking
Sora this Lord Ros you said he had wolf
masks those could only be obtained from
the shadow Dojo which we ured could not
be opened not without the energy of a
source
Dragon maybe RW stole energy from the
source Dragon Imperium captured captured
a source Dragon this Ros must be very
powerful indeed someone who could do
that to the greatest of the dragons
means true Darkness has poisoned the
world oh he's evil all right 100% even
his breath smells evil we came here to
learn to fight shatter spin but we
didn't realize the teachers were the
ones that defeated the Forbidden five
with you fighting alongside us there's
no way Ros can
win listen child when we took on the
Forbidden five We Were Young at the peak
of our powers we are old now the years
have taken their to ho we cannot fight
alongside
[Music]
you but we can train can we look at them
they are weak they are not ready they
passed all the tests they have proven
their worthiness and Who you calling
[Music]
weak they are not dragons you know my
opinion not after last time this is not
that time eagle we cannot ignore the
threat the blood moon brings with the
Realms now merged the five will have
even more to conquer more to
destroy and all of our work defeating
them banishing them will be for not our
Legacy
meaningless we must train
[Music]
them
fine you better not regret this so
you'll teach us to fight against shatter
spin we don't don't know how much time
we have But Rising Dragon technique is
extremely hard to master we start
training first thing in the morning we
can do it
overconfidence that's exactly the kind
of weakness The Forbidden five exploit
you have clearly been taught well but
you have only scratched the surface of
what you need to learn or ronu is right
this world is doomed
[Music]
these walls won't hold for
long look
out hey that's part of the portal gate
Nia told me about what's a portal gate
something we need to assemble together
if the portal is activated we can escape
hang on you know we can't just leave the
land of lost things the fog always sends
us back I I think we can leave now huh
what are you talking
about this is our only chance help me
assemble this thing
[Music]
cool where's it going to take us no
idea but anywhere is better than here
here goes nothing
[Music]
cool they've escaped it doesn't matter
where they go we will follow
Zane we why do you have a frog Man doll
it is a long and barely comprehensible
story doesn't matter we need your help
what seems to be the
problem them
[Music]